Ajay is
completely fooled till date, the earlier ones have set it, then
what about helmet or hair tie on it, on festivals
without ever thinking what will happen to helmet, this is
your condition, your condition, your hand is fooled, A A
[Music]
One lemon is bad, our sir, he takes a gesture,
sir, don't tell these snakes, he keeps them under control, let there be any disrespect to the
honour of Chironji, shame on me, sir, there will be
peace, suppress
this issue, you know a lot about bringing the mind and when it comes to
saving the same, you beat up those who are responsible for
your security, go and
save your loved ones with the helmet excuse